[{"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 44, "question": "Did you enjoy the status of television icon?", "qSentId": 43}, {"answer": "It certainly is, yes.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 52, "question": "It's better than the alternative, right?", "qSentId": 51}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's sort of like -- I'm not comparing myself to Dick Van Dyke, but I think there's a characteristic that can help you survive in television which is a kind of an affability, and a vulnerability.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 58, "question": "Why you?", "qSentId": 57}, {"answer": "You're that guy.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 62, "question": "Oh, well, you know?", "qSentId": 61}, {"answer": "Well, some of my --", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "How does it go down with all your famous friends?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "It's pretty lonely, but you know they seem to tolerate me somehow, because I can at least state myself eloquently and without actually kind of assuming what they -- the veneer of what they assume is what a Republican is, as some kind of nasty, strange villain that, you know, should be vilified and hated.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "Is it lonely out there?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "I'm sympathetic to some of the principles, but I'm not sure that the Tea Party has behavioral problem other than the ones that have been identified by people who are inimical to them.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "ORGAN: Are you -- are you sympathetic to the Tea Party element of the Republicans or is that a step too far?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 94, "question": "Nothing they say be objectionable to you at all?", "qSentId": 93}, {"answer": "Against it, yes.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 104, "question": "Against gay marriage?", "qSentId": 103}, {"answer": "Absolutely yes.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 109, "question": "I mean there are issues there, but you wouldn't agree with?", "qSentId": 108}, {"answer": "Yes, I've played several.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "You played a famous gay character?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "Well, OK, I think Barack Obama's election is a milestone for this country and a wonderful thing.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "And did you buy into all the hope, the audacity, the stuff that he apparently came with?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "Inspire, certainly.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 139, "question": "Isn't it incumbent on politicians, clearly president, to inspire their people?", "qSentId": 138}, {"answer": "Well, I would say greed.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "What is the simple answer?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "Right now I'm not gravitating toward a lot of people right now.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 158, "question": "Who do you like?", "qSentId": 157}, {"answer": "If I were advising them, I would just tell them that they must inspire people to assume that they have a right to make their own decisions about what dreams they wish to dream.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 171, "question": "Who do you think is more electable?", "qSentId": 170}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 175, "question": "What was my dream?", "qSentId": 174}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 178, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 177}, {"answer": "No, just wanted to be a working actor.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "Nothing more glamorous than that?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "Yes, I got a few more extras than I counted on.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 182, "question": "Have you fulfilled that?", "qSentId": 181}, {"answer": "Not quite.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 187, "question": "In terms of your acting aspirations, have you -- have you ticked all the boxes you wanted to tick?", "qSentId": 186}, {"answer": "RAMMER: There's certainly a lot left.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 189, "question": "What's left?", "qSentId": 188}, {"answer": "Well, I started out wanting to be a dramatic actor, ended up being a comedic actor, and now I've gone back to being a dramatic actor now.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "What's left on the acting block that you'd like to do?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "One role left to play.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 196, "question": "If you -- if you have one role left to play, what would it be?", "qSentId": 195}, {"answer": "Because they say your character in \"Boss\" is very King Lear-esque.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "What's the role?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "Iago is an interesting character because it's -- you know, it's the character that has the most words of any character in all the Shakespeare and it's almost every sentence is not iambic pentameter, it's iambic pentameter and a half.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 220, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 219}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 226, "question": "Is it just more fun being evil?", "qSentId": 225}, {"answer": "Yes -- no, it's a ball.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "It is, isn't it?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "You'll know when it comes up.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "What do you want from me?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "So, you did do the hard yards of theatrical trainings, didn't you, to be a serious actor?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "Gosh, Lawrence Olivier and Gregory Peck.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 258, "question": "Who were the actors you looked up to?", "qSentId": 257}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "Did you ever imagine at that stage, at Juilliard, you're looking around, all these talented people presumably -- did you ever imagine in your wildest dreams or maybe nightmares the level of fame that you would one day get through acting?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "And didn't always work really hard.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 271, "question": "Don't all actors doubt themselves?", "qSentId": 270}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 279, "question": "Well, that's -- that's sort of the flip side of narcissism, isn't it?", "qSentId": 278}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 300, "question": "In the back of your mind all you're thinking of is this could tank, and then what?", "qSentId": 299}, {"answer": "It's called an auger.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "Do we go to a hole in the ice with this little corks filthy and then just start fishing?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "I'm probably OK at it.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "Are you any good at doing that yourself?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "Kelsey Grammer is a guy who cares about people that has been trying to save the world because he couldn't save some things in his own life.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 345, "question": "What have you worked out about Kelsey Grammer?", "qSentId": 344}, {"answer": "RAMMER: Yes, we were together in school.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "You trained with him at the Juilliard, didn't you?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "But it's probably -- it's part of that because you managed to deal with so many of the demons?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "I mean for a while, it must be fun, isn't it, despite everything else?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "Well, there were -- there were several along the way.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "What was the -- what was the wake-up moment for you?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "Well, actually, I did go to Betty Ford and that helped.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "How did you manage to stop in the end?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "I have a drink sometimes, yes.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "Do you drink alcohol?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "Yes, yes.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "You can drink in moderation?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "It's interesting.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "How did it feel to you?", "qSentId": 466}, {"answer": "That was another night.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "Did she fire a gun at you?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "Yes, no, this is the -- this is what --", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 508, "question": "ORGAN: You married her after she shot at you?", "qSentId": 507}, {"answer": "I tell you, it was absurdly across -- a shot across the bow.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "Wasn't that a warning sign, get off it?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "So that fell apart pretty quickly.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 512, "question": "A woman shoots at me, I'm thinking twice about the marriage, you know?", "qSentId": 511}, {"answer": "Well, I have to -- I mean, I have to tell you, my -- \"The Real Housewives\" was my parting gift to her.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 533, "question": "This must have been like hell, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 532}, {"answer": "No, I think -- I think what I was trying to do was sell it to myself.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 551, "question": "Were you just charging around looking for true love and constantly believing you quickly found it?", "qSentId": 550}, {"answer": "Well, they're not good.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 562, "question": "But -- I mean, how are things?", "qSentId": 561}, {"answer": "We have no contact, no.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 564, "question": "Do you have any kind of dialogue with her?", "qSentId": 563}, {"answer": "Oh, it's great.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "How is your relationship with them?", "qSentId": 572}, {"answer": "RAMMER: Well, they're trying to -- they're doing their best to actually kind of make that difficult for me right now.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "You get plenty of access?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "No, I think she married me because I was Frasier.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "Do you think she married you because you were Kelsey Grammer, TV icon?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "I think it was Frasier.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 586, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 585}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I haven't been keeping track of everything, so there might be something that would surprise me.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 597, "question": "What's been worst thing, the most hurtful thing she said about you?", "qSentId": 596}, {"answer": "She once said that I didn't want my daughter.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 601, "question": "What's the most unfair labeling?", "qSentId": 600}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 604, "question": "Yes, well, it would, wouldn't it?", "qSentId": 603}, {"answer": "From Los Angeles.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 656, "question": "To England from New York?", "qSentId": 655}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 658, "question": "From Los Angeles?", "qSentId": 657}, {"answer": "Because Kayte is a very beautiful young lady, as we can see here.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 670, "question": "Well, you know what?", "qSentId": 669}, {"answer": "Oh, I think she knew who I was, but she didn't know who I am.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 701, "question": "Did she know who you were?", "qSentId": 700}, {"answer": "She believes in love.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 750, "question": "What is it about her you think that enabled her to deal with all this?", "qSentId": 749}, {"answer": "It's been -- it was a presumptive joy to go to work every day.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 776, "question": "Are you really enjoying it?", "qSentId": 775}, {"answer": "I love him.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 787, "question": "Do you like him or not?", "qSentId": 786}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 794, "question": "Isn't that you, in the end?", "qSentId": 793}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111227pmt", "aSentId": 816, "question": "Do you feel for the first you've gone back to the joy of life you had as a young boy?", "qSentId": 815}]